sportsretriever.com 2019-07-14

# Privacy Policy - Sports Retriever

Last Revised: April 30, 2018

Welcome to SportsretRiever (the “Website”, “our”, “we” or “us”). This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) is intended to describe our practices regarding the information we may collect from you when you use the Website, the manners in which we may use such information, and the choices and rights available to you.

1\. YOUR CONSENT  
BY ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW) IN THE EVENT YOU DECIDE TO PROVIDE US WITH SUCH. IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.  
Please note: you are not obligated by law to provide us with any Personal Information. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you are providing us with Personal Information at your own free will. You hereby agree that we may collect and use such Personal Information pursuant to this Privacy Policy and any applicable laws and regulations.

2\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM OUR USERS?  
• Non-personal Information: Un-identified and non-identifiable information pertaining to Users, which may be made available to us, or collected automatically via their use of the Website. Such Non-personal Information does not enable us to identify the person from whom it was collected, and mainly consists of technical and aggregated usage information which is not linked to an identifiable individual, such as the identity and operation system and browser, smart-phone version, operating system version, duration of usage of the Website, User’s ‘click-stream’ activity, keyboard language, etc.  
• Personal Information: Individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable efforts or together with additional information we have access to, enable the identification of an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature. Such Personal Information that is collected by us consists of the following types of information: IP address, device identifier, personal details provided in connection with usage of the Website, including name, e-mail address, phone number, address.  
We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Terms and the Privacy Policy.

3\. HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION ON OUR USERS?  
• We collect information through your use of the Website. In other words, we are aware of your usage of the Website and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, including by using “cookies” and other tracking technologies, as further detailed in Section ‎7 below.  
• We collect information which you provide us voluntarily. For example, we collect Personal information which you voluntarily provide when you use the Website or contact us.

4\. WHY DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION ON OUR USERS?  
• To provide and operate our Website and related services.  
• To display or send to you marketing and advertising material and general and personalized content and advertisement.  
• To be able to deliver and enhance the Website, provide the Users with technical assistance and support.  
• To send you updates, notices, notifications, announcements, and additional information related to the Website and related services.  
• To create cumulative statistical data and other cumulative information and/or other conclusive information that is non-personal, in which we and/or our business partners might make use of in order to operate and improve our Website and provide related services.  
• To comply with any applicable rule or regulation and/or response or defend against legal proceedings versus us or our affiliates. 

5\. LAWFUL GROUNDS FOR COLLECTING INFORMATION ON OUR USERS  
We collect and process your information for the purposes described in this policy, based at least on one of the following legal grounds:    
• With your consent: We ask for your agreement to process your information for specific purposes and you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. For example, we ask for your consent to provide you with personalized content and ads through the use of cookies;  
• Legitimate interests: We process your information for our legitimate interests while applying appropriate safeguards that protect your privacy. This means that we process your information for things like detecting, preventing, or otherwise addressing fraud, abuse, security, usability, functionality or technical issues with our services, protecting against harm to the rights, property or safety of our properties, or our users, or the public as required or permitted by law; Enforcing legal claims, including investigation of potential violations of this Privacy Policy; in order to comply and/or fulfil our obligation under applicable laws, regulation, guidelines, industry standards and contractual requirements, legal process, subpoena or governmental request, as well as our Terms of Service. 

6\. WHERE DO WE STORE USER’S PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
Information regarding the Users will be maintained, processed and stored by us and our authorized affiliates and service providers in the United States, and as necessary, in secured cloud storage, provided by our third party service provider.  
While the data protection laws in the above jurisdictions may be different than the laws of your residence or location, please know that we, our affiliates and our service providers that store or process your Personal Information on the our behalf are each committed to keep it protected and secured, pursuant to this Privacy Policy and industry standards, regardless of any lesser legal requirements that may apply in their jurisdiction.  
You hereby accept the place of storage and the transfer of information as described above. 

7\. WHO DO WE SHARE USER INFORMATION WITH AND WHY?  
We may share your Personal Information with third parties (or otherwise allow them access to it) only in the following manners and instances:  
• To satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request, whenever we believes in good faith that it is legally bound to share such information  
• To enforce this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use including investigation of potential violations thereof  
• To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues  
• To respond to User’s support requests  
• To respond to claims that contact information or any other private or proprietary information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been used, posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment  
• To protect the rights, property, or personal safety of us, our Users or the general public  
• When we undergo any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets  
• To collect, hold and/or manage Users’ Personal Information through our authorized third party service providers , as contemplated hereunder, who may be located outside of Israel (for example: Google Analytics, Amazon Web Services, Hotjar) Such third party services providers may receive or otherwise have access to our Users’ Personal Information, depending on each of their particular roles and purposes in facilitating and enhancing our Website and related services, namely to allow cloud hosting services, serving of personalized content and advertisement, analytics of the functionality and usability of our Website. and may only use it for such purposes  
• Pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure.  
For avoidance of doubt, we may share anonymized or de-identified information with any other third party, at our sole discretion.

8\. USING COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES  
We use certain monitoring and tracking technologies, including ones offered by third party service providers. These technologies are used in order to maintain, provide and improve our website on an ongoing basis, and in order to provide a better experience to our Users. For example, these technologies enable us to: (i) keep track of our Users’ preferences and authenticated sessions, (ii) secure our website by detecting abnormal behaviors, (iii) identify technical issues and improve the overall performance of our website, (iv) create and monitor analytics, and (v) deliver you targeted advertisements that are more tailored to you based on your browsing activities and inferred interests and track ad performance (For more information about this practice, click here: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).  
Please see our Cookie Policy at: <http://www.sportsretriever.com/cookie-policy/>  
Learn more about your choices and how to opt-out of tracking technologies:  
In order to delete or block any tracking technologies, please refer to the “Help” area on your internet browser for further instructions, or You may also opt out of third party tracking technologies by following the instructions provided by each third party service provider in its privacy policy listed above or visiting www.youronlinechoices.eu. Please note however that deleting any of our tracking technologies or disabling future tracking technologies may prevent you from accessing certain areas or features of our website, or may otherwise adversely affect your user experience.

9\. MINORS  
To use our website, you must be over the age of sixteen (16). Therefore, we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors under the age of sixteen (16) and do not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of sixteen (16) are not using the Website. 

10\. INFORMATION SECURITY  
We employ industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users’ Personal Information, reduce the risks stemming from loss of information and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. However, no measure can provide absolute information security.

11\. DATA RETENTION  
We retain the Personal Information we collect only for as long as needed in order to provide you with our services and to comply with applicable laws and regulations. We then either delete from our systems or anonymize it without further notice to you.  
If you withdraw your consent to us processing your Personal Information, we will delete your Personal Information from our systems (except to the extent such data in whole or in part to comply with any applicable rule or regulation and/or response or defend against legal proceedings versus us or our affiliates).

12\. UPDATING, OBTAINING A COPY OF, OR DELETING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
If the law applicable to you grants you such rights, you may ask to access, correct, or delete your Personal Information that is stored in our systems. You may also ask for our confirmation as to whether or not we process your Personal Information.  
Subject to the limitations in law, you may request that we update, correct, or delete inaccurate or outdated information. You may also request that we suspend the use of any Personal Information whose accuracy you contest while we verify the status of that data.  
Subject the limitations in law, you may also be entitled to obtain the Personal Information you directly provided us (excluding data we obtained from other sources) in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and may have the right to transmit such data to another party.  
If you wish to exercise any of these rights, contact us at: [info@sportsretriever.com](mailto:info@sportsretriever.com). When handling these requests we may ask for additional information to confirm your identity and your request. Please note, upon request to delete your Personal Information, we may retain such data in whole or in part to comply with any applicable rule or regulation and/or response or defend against legal proceedings versus us or our affiliates  
To find out whether these rights apply to you and on any other privacy related matter, you can contact your local data protection authority if you have concerns regarding your rights under local law.

13\. UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will notify you regarding substantial changes of this Privacy Policy by changing the link to the Privacy Policy in the Website. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Website. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Website after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

14\. GENERAL INFORMATION  
This Privacy Policy, its interpretation, and any claims and disputes related hereto, shall be governed by the laws of the State of Israel, without respect to its criminal law principles. Any and all such claims and disputes shall be brought in, and you hereby consent to them being litigated in and decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Tel Aviv, Israel.  
This Privacy Policy was written in English, and may be translated into other languages for your convenience. If a translated (non-English) version of this Privacy Policy conflicts in any way with the English version, the provisions of the English version shall prevail.

15\. HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?  
If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us an email at: [info@sportsretriever.com](mailto:info@sportsretriever.com) and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe.
